

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Meticulous UI/UX Designer & Front-End Developer with 3+ years of experience and passion for responsive web design and modern mobile app design. Hoping to share my skills, expertise, and experience with a progressive and forward-thinking company to increase and enhance my experience.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer & Front-End Developer

Takkat Solutions, Menouf

Jul 2019 – Jan 2022

- Collaborates closely with the app development team to bring prototypes into the production code process.
- Test websites during the development process for usability and fixing bugs.
- Ensure that the website front-end is free from errors or bugs.
- Develop reusable code for future use.
- Optimize web pages for maximum speed and boost their scalability.

UI/UX Designer & Front-End Developer

NTS Co., The 5th Settlement

Apr 2018 - Jun 2019

- Knowledge of current web design techniques and trends.
- Building wireframes and prototypes which were then turned into functional and responsive digital products.
- Implements user-focused designs and processes in order to identify specific user needs and find best solutions.
- Translate websites and app documentation into a high quality UI designs.
- Plan and design the structure and design of web pages.

Front-End Developer

Creadev, Shebin Elkom

Mar 2017 - Mar 2018

- Knowledge into design and creation of effectual user interfaces.
- Translate UI designs into high quality and responsive web design.
- Capability and willingness to study new software applications.

CONTACT

Phone

01005563956

Email

ucef.sale7@gmail.com

Portfolio

YusufSaleh.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science, Menoufia University | May 2021

RELEVANT SKILLS

Web Design

UI/UX Design

Vue JS

React JS

JavaScript

jQuery

UIKit

Bootstrap

GitHub

TFS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe XD

Microsoft Office